Hui-Ming Peng

Backend Developer

Email: hero19931012@gmail.com

SUMMARY

Passionate and ambitious programming learner, very willing to take new skills or tools.

Proficient in web backend development with NodeJS, RMDBS or NoSQL and server environment configuration. Familiar with frontend development, can build simple blog with React. Have experience in deploying shopping web application on AWS EC2, and have basic understanding with building cluster on GCP using kubernetes.

EXPERIENCE

2021/2-NOW

Backend Developer

TWISTER5 CO. LTD.

Responsible for the back-end development of the big data management platform, using NestJS framework, writing in TypeScript, using Elasticsearch and Logstash to deal with data acquisition, parsing and query

Features:

- Database mapping design
- Customizable dashboard charts
- Abnormal monitoring and alerting service
- Periodically reporting sending service

2020/6-2021/12

Student LIDEMY

- Learning web front/back end development knowledge and skills
- Developed Parlando

2018/12-2020/2

Research Assistant GEM FONT CORP.

Meat products formulation and process design

SKILLS

- Backend: Node, JavaScript, TypeScript, NestJS, Express, Elasticsearch, Logstash, MySQL, Linux
- Frontend: React, Html, Scss
- Cloud: AWS EC2, GCP
- Tools: Docker, Kubernetes

EDUCATION

- Master of Animal Science, National Chung Hsing University, July 2018
- Bacheler of Animal Science, National Chiayi University, July 2016